[{"front": "\u52fa", "id": "1419243725829", "back": "\u52fa <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/94a2085a-d540-44f8-b558-46afee51dc9a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u52fa\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u52fa\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ch\u01b0\u1edbc"}, {"front": "b\u1ea1ch<div><br /></div>", "id": "1419243910844", "back": "b\u1ea1ch<div><br /></div>  <hr id=answer>  \u767d  <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/a886b58e-5ca4-4b9f-84e7-469f5a42444d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u767d \">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u767d \">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5fd9", "id": "1421547355107", "back": "\u5fd9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d3482cde-6134-4173-8d8c-ddd98d534c85/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5fd9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5fd9\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  mang (busy)"}, {"front": "\u672a", "id": "1421547940247", "back": "\u672a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/775a06d3-ffbb-4468-b715-d60622e64f32/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u672a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u672a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  v\u1ecb, m\u00f9i (not yet, zodiac)"}, {"front": "h\u1eefu (friend)", "id": "1421548928508", "back": "h\u1eefu (friend)  <hr id=answer>  \u53cb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6220b8d6-b558-408e-9744-f77be02eecdb/ \">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53cb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53cb\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "khuy\u1ec3n (dog, radical)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u72ad</div>", "id": "1421831052391", "back": "khuy\u1ec3n (dog, radical)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u72ad</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u72ac <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/36d6738b-b338-438f-95c6-80ab55515810/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u72ac\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u72ac\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "gia (father, title for superior)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u723a</div>", "id": "1422172311850", "back": "gia (father, title for superior)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u723a</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u7237 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9fa61756-1d2c-4178-8344-c9ffe8b61878/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7237\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7237\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "h\u1ee9a (permit, promise, very)", "id": "1422173130995", "back": "h\u1ee9a (permit, promise, very)  <hr id=answer>  \u8bb8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d3e5de80-380b-44d6-9996-e467a10186c3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bb8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bb8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6208", "id": "1422175695658", "back": "\u6208 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/71f2022a-d0b4-4002-9839-0cae0ca6cffd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6208\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6208\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  qua (halberd)"}, {"front": "\u4eac", "id": "1422261868751", "back": "\u4eac <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c73be64a-6e93-46a2-afdd-a990410848cd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4eac\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4eac\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  kinh (capital, great)"}, {"front": "\u5382", "id": "1422438499715", "back": "\u5382 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/62d9a2a4-e091-4134-9673-fad20de5ea7f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5382\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5382\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  x\u01b0\u1edfng (factory),&nbsp;h\u00e1n (cliff)<div>&nbsp;\u5ee0</div>"}, {"front": "\u620a", "id": "1422952979897", "back": "\u620a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e6faafb0-82dc-46ae-ba5e-afcccde98ccc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u620a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u620a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u1eadu (fifth Celestial Stem)"}, {"front": "m\u1eadu (fifth Celestial Stem)", "id": "1422952979898", "back": "m\u1eadu (fifth Celestial Stem)  <hr id=answer>  \u620a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e6faafb0-82dc-46ae-ba5e-afcccde98ccc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u620a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u620a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5151", "id": "1423298472948", "back": "\u5151 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/cb1e3e06-e1b7-4a68-86c2-aca49a10f38d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5151\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5151\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111o\u00e1i, \u0111o\u00e0i (cash, exchange,&nbsp;second of the eight trigrams/west)&nbsp;"}, {"front": "th\u00f9y (suspend/hang down, pass to next generation, almost/nearly, condescend)", "id": "1423301454922", "back": "th\u00f9y (suspend/hang down, pass to next generation, almost/nearly, condescend)  <hr id=answer>  \u5782 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/d510256c-2954-4143-a110-fd4349c90d49/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5782\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5782\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "m\u1ed7 (someone/something, I)", "id": "1423748972858", "back": "m\u1ed7 (someone/something, I)  <hr id=answer>  \u67d0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/8c5a4032-999b-4e9f-b184-a8be47eeeb71/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u67d0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u67d0\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "thi\u1ec3u, thi\u1ebfu (little, missing/absent/wanting)", "id": "1424936542764", "back": "thi\u1ec3u, thi\u1ebfu (little, missing/absent/wanting)  <hr id=answer>  \u5c11 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/bebc1310-17bf-4b35-b3ef-8414b87a7f6b/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c11\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c11\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "h\u01b0u (rest/stop/cease, joy/happiness)", "id": "1424938385045", "back": "h\u01b0u (rest/stop/cease, joy/happiness)  <hr id=answer>  \u4f11 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9f3b7bf9-e407-4295-a32f-bf59e87cb352/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f11\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f11\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "n\u1ed9 (anger, vigorous, sprout forth)&nbsp;", "id": "1424942119293", "back": "n\u1ed9 (anger, vigorous, sprout forth)&nbsp;  <hr id=answer>  \u6012 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2de78952-f422-4b45-9477-09b30d67b207/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6012\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6012\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "phi (fly, fleeting/unsubstantial/surprise)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u98db</div>", "id": "1424995529133", "back": "phi (fly, fleeting/unsubstantial/surprise)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u98db</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u98de <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/1b48792f-518a-4f2e-baf1-7f0df1242012/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u98de\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u98de\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7b11", "id": "1425285228517", "back": "\u7b11 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/c9a576b1-385f-44a1-8551-8be09ddaa864/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7b11\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7b11\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ti\u1ebfu (laugh/deride)"}, {"front": "\u79cb", "id": "1425285335083", "back": "\u79cb <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0d526f96-4898-4cce-bcc8-ec2d828f4d2a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u79cb\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u79cb\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  thu (autumn, year/old age)"}, {"front": "\u544a", "id": "1425406332736", "back": "\u544a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9991a2ea-c4c1-4ed2-a82c-3ac36f429bec/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u544a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u544a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u00e1o (tell/announce, accuse)"}, {"front": "\u7231", "id": "1425408006725", "back": "\u7231 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9f237782-b424-4a9f-87be-54c2f2d78a52/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7231\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7231\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u00e1i (love, favor)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u611b</div>"}, {"front": "ng\u1ed9t (high/flat, ignorant-looking, punish by cutting off the feet)", "id": "1425429290461", "back": "ng\u1ed9t (high/flat, ignorant-looking, punish by cutting off the feet)  <hr id=answer>  \u5140 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/94c6bb5a-8e21-40a1-b73f-0ea7077004a9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5140\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5140\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "nha (teeth, ivory, bite)", "id": "1425720523190", "back": "nha (teeth, ivory, bite)  <hr id=answer>  \u7259 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/6dabed04-cdd3-4988-8d23-1113a9070212/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7259\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7259\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u6240", "id": "1426327286731", "back": "\u6240 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2489ad64-9c45-4b13-8381-d30a12b96eef/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6240\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6240\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  s\u1edf (place/location, unit for room/building, which/those that)"}, {"front": "th\u01b0\u01a1ng (trade, discuss/exchange, math division)", "id": "1426584192863", "back": "th\u01b0\u01a1ng (trade, discuss/exchange, math division)  <hr id=answer>  \u5546 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/0bf650a7-03ce-4671-8f9a-e95701180689/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5546\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5546\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u957f", "id": "1430560553831", "back": "\u957f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/ae4f753d-aa05-4905-90af-3c62cbe78295/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u957f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u957f\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tr\u01b0\u1eddng (long), tr\u01b0\u1edfng (senior/old/chief, increase/grow)<div><br /></div><div>&nbsp;\u9577</div>"}, {"front": "\u76f4", "id": "1430560664508", "back": "\u76f4 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/9a421452-9423-4a97-b207-5ddee0ffeb84/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u76f4\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u76f4\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tr\u1ef1c (straight, just/only)"}, {"front": "ti\u1ec7p (win/triumph, swift/quick, spoil of war)", "id": "1431078338749", "back": "ti\u1ec7p (win/triumph, swift/quick, spoil of war)  <hr id=answer>  \u6377 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/02f67a7b-aee5-4931-85e0-0e38422a4e57/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6377\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6377\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "ch\u1ea9m (how/why/what)", "id": "1431079150549", "back": "ch\u1ea9m (how/why/what)  <hr id=answer>  \u600e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/e56a044c-5f41-45e9-91bd-018bd6405f6c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u600e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u600e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "t\u1ed1i (supreme, very/most/extreme)", "id": "1431080971960", "back": "t\u1ed1i (supreme, very/most/extreme)  <hr id=answer>  \u6700 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/46970aea-7e7f-43bd-a559-4dcf8c3dd204/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6700\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6700\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4f0a", "id": "1432684811217", "back": "\u4f0a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/de46ec27-aea1-4bc6-9d42-d98c408067ec/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f0a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f0a\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  y (he/she, family name, transcription sound for -i-)"}, {"front": "ch\u1ec9 (paper)", "id": "1432707833716", "back": "ch\u1ec9 (paper)  <hr id=answer>  \u7eb8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/99ae8c59-5e2c-49e0-8ea1-ac569faddced/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7eb8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7eb8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u524c", "id": "1433977665931", "back": "\u524c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/06dd122d-a8a6-4149-9e10-eff3240fdda9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u524c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u524c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u1ea1t (slash open, disagreeable/rebellious)"}, {"front": "ta (a small number, a few)", "id": "1436167988194", "back": "ta (a small number, a few)  <hr id=answer>  \u4e9b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/6721759/2d6eaa97-d7cf-4c8b-9190-b65818241bd8/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e9b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e9b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u535c", "id": "1437267608897", "back": "\u535c <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/81e0b969-6cdc-4f77-9fc3-d736dbbd41b6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u535c\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u535c\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u1ed1c (select)"}, {"front": "\u79ef", "id": "1437268019627", "back": "\u79ef <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/a1a7b0ad-752e-41df-bd35-fa4093d01904/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u79ef\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u79ef\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u00edch (accumulate, multiplication/product)"}, {"front": "t\u00edch (accumulate, multiplication/product)", "id": "1437268019628", "back": "t\u00edch (accumulate, multiplication/product)  <hr id=answer>  \u79ef <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/a1a7b0ad-752e-41df-bd35-fa4093d01904/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u79ef\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u79ef\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u00e1 (inferior, Asia)", "id": "1437268524459", "back": "\u00e1 (inferior, Asia)  <hr id=answer>  \u4e9a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/06907ae9-dd14-40fc-8a04-979c8765e5ce/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e9a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e9a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5c14", "id": "1437892945385", "back": "\u5c14 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/f656b1b6-1e78-43e1-904b-63e920a5e56a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c14\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c14\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  nh\u0129 (thus, so; transcription for -er-)"}, {"front": "c\u1ea5p (grant/provide/give)", "id": "1437893377348", "back": "c\u1ea5p (grant/provide/give)  <hr id=answer>  \u7ed9 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/c3d4a9a5-bf3b-40a9-8235-10fdbc725e03/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7ed9\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7ed9\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "gia (ba gia: tomato, transcription sound)", "id": "1437894700573", "back": "gia (ba gia: tomato, transcription sound)  <hr id=answer>  \u8304 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/d2709b63-e088-4a24-9349-b0087a03869e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8304\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8304\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "th\u1ecb (C\u00e2y h\u1ed3ng)", "id": "1439192313713", "back": "th\u1ecb (C\u00e2y h\u1ed3ng)  <hr id=answer>  \u67ff <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/bf1a2a74-9979-4962-b4c8-d166b25e6541/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u67ff\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u67ff\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u77db", "id": "1439192548492", "back": "\u77db <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/16ca1f9a-0dd8-4391-b263-32312236d7f6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u77db\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u77db\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  m\u00e2u (gi\u00e1o, c\u00e1n d\u00e0i c\u00f3 m\u0169i nh\u1ecdn)"}, {"front": "t\u1ea3 (Mi\u00eau t\u1ea3; writing)", "id": "1439192719134", "back": "t\u1ea3 (Mi\u00eau t\u1ea3; writing)  <hr id=answer>  \u5199 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/342b8723-fb4f-47ba-8b40-3e4a02c56df2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5199\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5199\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "ti\u1ebft (holiday;&nbsp;L\u1ec5 nghi; details; section/period/part)<div>\u7bc0</div>", "id": "1439192886635", "back": "ti\u1ebft (holiday;&nbsp;L\u1ec5 nghi; details; section/period/part)<div>\u7bc0</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u8282 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/39c6d838-2034-4b06-8928-e1f5c79418e7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8282\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8282\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "t\u1ecb (chi th\u1ee9 s\u00e1u trong m\u01b0\u1eddi hai chi;&nbsp;ch\u00edn gi\u1edd s\u00e1ng \u0111\u1ebfn m\u01b0\u1eddi m\u1ed9t gi\u1edd tr\u01b0a)", "id": "1439192923192", "back": "t\u1ecb (chi th\u1ee9 s\u00e1u trong m\u01b0\u1eddi hai chi;&nbsp;ch\u00edn gi\u1edd s\u00e1ng \u0111\u1ebfn m\u01b0\u1eddi m\u1ed9t gi\u1edd tr\u01b0a)  <hr id=answer>  \u5df3 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/71da0233-f8a6-4924-8c1a-6c273eeb62cb/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5df3\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5df3\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "t\u1ed1 (do/make)", "id": "1439193040198", "back": "t\u1ed1 (do/make)  <hr id=answer>  \u505a <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/1958d313-0816-4205-a49f-801b1749d2e9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u505a\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u505a\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "nghi (suspicious, questioning)", "id": "1439193135185", "back": "nghi (suspicious, questioning)  <hr id=answer>  \u7591 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/102c85e2-722a-4507-aa67-4208e1d038e4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7591\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7591\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4e5e", "id": "1439193181132", "back": "\u4e5e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/667be6df-8501-4591-b1a0-2c889cca6726/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e5e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e5e\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  kh\u1ea5t (beg)"}, {"front": "h\u00e0i (child/kid)", "id": "1439193416492", "back": "h\u00e0i (child/kid)  <hr id=answer>  \u5b69 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/bdf1eb18-302a-4d48-a681-c2662c3bb029/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b69\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b69\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "c\u1ea9u (dog)", "id": "1439193436959", "back": "c\u1ea9u (dog)  <hr id=answer>  \u72d7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/c7929308-a397-4538-aee9-524a83606ed5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u72d7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u72d7\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "tha (it, pronoun for things), \u0111\u00e0 (camel)", "id": "1439329883646", "back": "tha (it, pronoun for things), \u0111\u00e0 (camel)  <hr id=answer>  \u5b83 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/e5ed04e2-a536-46f1-8ced-014c471aaea3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b83\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b83\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "thi\u1ebft (iron)<div>\u9435</div>", "id": "1439330416189", "back": "thi\u1ebft (iron)<div>\u9435</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u94c1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/aa3bc84e-43e1-4913-a912-de46d7301a58/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u94c1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u94c1\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u61c2", "id": "1439514610753", "back": "\u61c2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/b4a92402-ab95-4f30-9429-ba4b8a1abefc/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u61c2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u61c2\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u1ed5ng (understand)"}, {"front": "c\u1ea3m (feeling)", "id": "1439798067299", "back": "c\u1ea3m (feeling)  <hr id=answer>  \u611f <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/36078213-3111-4a04-84a3-9f2067717881/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u611f\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u611f\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "l\u01b0u (stream, flow, class)", "id": "1440320533724", "back": "l\u01b0u (stream, flow, class)  <hr id=answer>  \u6d41 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/4554d1d2-3156-4e79-a63c-edad81b90b58/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6d41\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6d41\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5efa", "id": "1440320582758", "back": "\u5efa <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/96b0e9f6-f8b0-4fa2-bf43-89fc59485da7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5efa\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5efa\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  ki\u1ebfn (architect, build)"}, {"front": "\u8ddf", "id": "1440320706371", "back": "\u8ddf <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/20ae96d6-5877-4628-85eb-d94d87b7c7d2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8ddf\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8ddf\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u00e2n, ng\u00e2n (heel, follow, toward)"}, {"front": "\u8bb2", "id": "1440320816054", "back": "\u8bb2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/27b86bc9-5573-406a-8b12-8511a22e1012/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bb2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bb2\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u8b1b gi\u1ea3ng (explain)"}, {"front": "\u4fd7", "id": "1440321696553", "back": "\u4fd7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/6d5ee592-0699-4d97-9ffc-36c54fbd82db/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4fd7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4fd7\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ee5c (customs, vulgar)"}, {"front": "kh\u00fac (turn, bend; numerary for song)", "id": "1440321741325", "back": "kh\u00fac (turn, bend; numerary for song)  <hr id=answer>  \u66f2 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/5130dbcd-64d5-4b21-b8ac-792f4e12e3b6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u66f2\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u66f2\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "d\u1ecbch (change), d\u1ecb (easy)", "id": "1440405144542", "back": "d\u1ecbch (change), d\u1ecb (easy)  <hr id=answer>  \u6613 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/b1aa9e2c-ee44-441f-9f55-1090b446dce7/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6613\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6613\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ec1 (forehead, headline, topic/essay)", "id": "1440405245903", "back": "\u0111\u1ec1 (forehead, headline, topic/essay)  <hr id=answer>  \u9898 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/0cf7a76f-6a20-4b3c-be76-7180899d102c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9898\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9898\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "ph\u00f3ng (send/throw)", "id": "1440405401893", "back": "ph\u00f3ng (send/throw)  <hr id=answer>  \u653e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/7a3570e2-044c-434b-9887-9e4f885ce9be/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u653e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u653e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "gi\u1ea3 (fake)", "id": "1440405485461", "back": "gi\u1ea3 (fake)  <hr id=answer>  \u5047 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/b4722bea-54a9-4084-91c3-c4b27f888822/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5047\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5047\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u65c5", "id": "1440621451534", "back": "\u65c5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/44264132-7495-4829-b8bc-ba58af569855/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65c5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65c5\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  l\u1eef (division/army, travel)"}, {"front": "l\u1eef (division/army, travel)", "id": "1440621451535", "back": "l\u1eef (division/army, travel)  <hr id=answer>  \u65c5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/44264132-7495-4829-b8bc-ba58af569855/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u65c5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u65c5\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7da0 l\u1ee5c (green, chlorine)", "id": "1440621981900", "back": "\u7da0 l\u1ee5c (green, chlorine)  <hr id=answer>  \u7eff <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/a7df12c6-97cf-4286-b7e3-0d36e3d5a47c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7eff\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7eff\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u80de", "id": "1440657314515", "back": "\u80de <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/b62ec6d2-dea2-43d8-9533-91e4b3af8272/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u80de\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u80de\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u00e0o (amniotic sac)"}, {"front": "\u4ed1", "id": "1440659608045", "back": "\u4ed1 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/c42e6ec0-fbe8-4cde-afc4-fb0406dd9c34/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ed1\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ed1\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u4f96 lu\u00e2n, l\u00f4n (order)"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ed5ng (last name, manage)", "id": "1440660210106", "back": "\u0111\u1ed5ng (last name, manage)  <hr id=answer>  \u8463 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/f4b5fe29-422d-4166-8e17-410a8b1404c6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8463\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8463\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u91cd", "id": "1440660301659", "back": "\u91cd <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/0397577d-ea61-4d4d-9313-b174168a4828/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u91cd\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u91cd\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tr\u1ecdng (heavy), tr\u00f9ng (repeat/duplicate)"}, {"front": "\u1ea9m (drink)", "id": "1440660500861", "back": "\u1ea9m (drink)  <hr id=answer>  \u996e <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/512fb9d7-511d-47b1-952a-e0d3e734f18f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u996e\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u996e\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "c\u1ed1c (grain, valley)", "id": "1440660529034", "back": "c\u1ed1c (grain, valley)  <hr id=answer>  \u8c37 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/f38d6ae3-d6b4-498d-9566-a8a16df4a605/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8c37\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8c37\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u53ec", "id": "1440661037197", "back": "\u53ec <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770343/8e1891e1-a2eb-443b-99ba-bb051eb8ab03/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53ec\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53ec\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tri\u1ec7u (summon, invite)"}, {"front": "\u9304 l\u1ee5c (copy/record, select/hire)", "id": "1441410726049", "back": "\u9304 l\u1ee5c (copy/record, select/hire)  <hr id=answer>  \u5f55 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/11379c51-44c2-4871-a7c8-121363015b63/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5f55\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5f55\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "l\u00e1nh (other)", "id": "1441410863209", "back": "l\u00e1nh (other)  <hr id=answer>  \u53e6 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/544ce55e-472f-48dc-b56d-6859173d6b25/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53e6\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53e6\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5eda tr\u00f9 (kitchen; chest)", "id": "1441410999612", "back": "\u5eda tr\u00f9 (kitchen; chest)  <hr id=answer>  \u53a8 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/78601038-6855-4694-9b19-4b004f7a2506/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u53a8\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u53a8\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8457 tr\u1ee9 (write, clear), tr\u01b0\u1edbc (in progress), tr\u1eef<div>to catch, to receive, to suffer, to make move, to take action, auxiliary word (always behind verb)</div>", "id": "1441411909237", "back": "\u8457 tr\u1ee9 (write, clear), tr\u01b0\u1edbc (in progress), tr\u1eef<div>to catch, to receive, to suffer, to make move, to take action, auxiliary word (always behind verb)</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u7740 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/e80dcccf-3dbf-4ea3-90ec-273e40a4651a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7740\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7740\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "nhi\u00ean (but, such)", "id": "1442735862515", "back": "nhi\u00ean (but, such)  <hr id=answer>  \u7136 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/0cc90639-40e5-4561-91e9-990d3b63d529/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7136\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7136\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u820d", "id": "1442735898910", "back": "\u820d <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/87d70a7c-5dc5-432e-b173-83868ecf54d0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u820d\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u820d\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  x\u00e1 (house/housing)"}, {"front": "\u5e63 t\u1ec7 (money)", "id": "1442736195071", "back": "\u5e63 t\u1ec7 (money)  <hr id=answer>  \u5e01 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/006fc60b-fa43-430c-9125-cc47c9c24338/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e01\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e01\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u54e1 vi\u00ean (person/member, measure word for certain kinds of people such as army generals)", "id": "1442736876731", "back": "\u54e1 vi\u00ean (person/member, measure word for certain kinds of people such as army generals)  <hr id=answer>  \u5458 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/a2192ae2-fc35-4437-a39f-5241e0b092c4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5458\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5458\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4ec7", "id": "1442736997054", "back": "\u4ec7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/237b3726-d742-4839-a18a-b92721e308d3/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ec7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ec7\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u1eebu (feud/animosity)"}, {"front": "\u5b98", "id": "1443945426620", "back": "\u5b98 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/a69112ca-1dd0-4959-91ce-f3780c05bcfd/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5b98\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5b98\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  quan (official, body organ)"}, {"front": "\u5a41 l\u00e2u, l\u0169, lu&nbsp;(a star, last name Lou)", "id": "1443945476833", "back": "\u5a41 l\u00e2u, l\u0169, lu&nbsp;(a star, last name Lou)  <hr id=answer>  \u5a04&nbsp; <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/d1d41c30-aa61-4931-b795-80917f945183/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5a04&nbsp;\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5a04&nbsp;\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5510", "id": "1443945642804", "back": "\u5510 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/ccbdcf03-9ff3-4710-a60c-afcf9af146e0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5510\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5510\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u0111\u01b0\u1eddng (Chinese dynasty)"}, {"front": "\u9526", "id": "1443945747971", "back": "\u9526 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/cde13457-ea2d-4968-ad83-5fc68bac624a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9526\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9526\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  c\u1ea9m (G\u1ea5m;&nbsp;Nhi\u1ec1u th\u1ee9, nhi\u1ec1u m\u00f3n)"}, {"front": "c\u1ea9m (G\u1ea5m;&nbsp;Nhi\u1ec1u th\u1ee9, nhi\u1ec1u m\u00f3n)", "id": "1443945747972", "back": "c\u1ea9m (G\u1ea5m;&nbsp;Nhi\u1ec1u th\u1ee9, nhi\u1ec1u m\u00f3n)  <hr id=answer>  \u9526 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/cde13457-ea2d-4968-ad83-5fc68bac624a/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9526\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9526\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u4f65", "id": "1443945782763", "back": "\u4f65 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/a51e1813-f4c2-4149-b444-510f2c3e4da0/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4f65\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4f65\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  \u50c9 thi\u00eam (all)"}, {"front": "\u7eaa", "id": "1443945838551", "back": "\u7eaa <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/9ec9a7a3-b52b-4a5a-9226-ccf7336605c9/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7eaa\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7eaa\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  k\u1ec9 (record, law/rule/discipline, age/era/period)"}, {"front": "tra (look up, investigate)", "id": "1443945863685", "back": "tra (look up, investigate)  <hr id=answer>  \u67e5 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/02720cb4-7a69-4443-997f-91fc3347ab37/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u67e5\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u67e5\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "t\u00f2ng (from)<div>\u5f9e</div>", "id": "1448523495634", "back": "t\u00f2ng (from)<div>\u5f9e</div>  <hr id=answer>  \u4ece <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/487b4fea-eff5-4325-a77f-cede327d1d1d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4ece\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4ece\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "nha (exclamation word)", "id": "1448523529980", "back": "nha (exclamation word)  <hr id=answer>  \u5440 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/dbfab595-454e-4a6c-af2e-c37df4c27c13/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5440\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5440\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "h\u1ecda (drawing)", "id": "1448523589783", "back": "h\u1ecda (drawing)  <hr id=answer>  \u753b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/590730a0-d433-4000-8908-c3613b4e1b7f/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u753b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u753b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u7b51", "id": "1448523797754", "back": "\u7b51 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/039efceb-1c00-4bd5-afcd-c13cce1c019c/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7b51\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7b51\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tr\u00fac (build/building)<div>\u7bc9</div>"}, {"front": "\u8bbe", "id": "1448523831059", "back": "\u8bbe <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/7f4d6121-b146-4f7d-8d51-42c7f00d2fc1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bbe\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bbe\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  thi\u1ebft (design/build, found/set up)"}, {"front": "thi\u1ebft (design/build, found/set up)", "id": "1448523831060", "back": "thi\u1ebft (design/build, found/set up)  <hr id=answer>  \u8bbe <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/7f4d6121-b146-4f7d-8d51-42c7f00d2fc1/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8bbe\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8bbe\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u8272", "id": "1448523845035", "back": "\u8272 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/e3527c2c-b8ac-4ae3-a18b-ac5cb3d86c7d/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u8272\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u8272\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  s\u1eafc"}, {"front": "\u5ea7", "id": "1448523895682", "back": "\u5ea7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/22438c96-2387-47fe-9e6a-4e3078d67af4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5ea7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5ea7\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  t\u1ecda, t\u00f2a (numerary for building/moutain/large solid things, seat/base/stand)"}, {"front": "t\u1ecda, t\u00f2a (numerary for building/moutain/large solid things, seat/base/stand)", "id": "1448523895683", "back": "t\u1ecda, t\u00f2a (numerary for building/moutain/large solid things, seat/base/stand)  <hr id=answer>  \u5ea7 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/22438c96-2387-47fe-9e6a-4e3078d67af4/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5ea7\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5ea7\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u0111\u00e1p (respond, requite)", "id": "1448523962184", "back": "\u0111\u00e1p (respond, requite)  <hr id=answer>  \u7b54 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/65887fc9-46d6-4e05-b11a-ef0ee5065bbe/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u7b54\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u7b54\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u9648", "id": "1448524072946", "back": "\u9648 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/1c46e1be-0ae8-451c-80b4-0a611aa27490/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u9648\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u9648\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  tr\u1ea7n (last name, explain/tell)"}, {"front": "\u5c04", "id": "1448524183579", "back": "\u5c04 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/d90e3cb7-bd65-49e1-92a4-f4031c1af0a6/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5c04\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5c04\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  x\u1ea1 (shoot)"}, {"front": "\u5723", "id": "1448524249779", "back": "\u5723 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/aae8ea48-8416-4638-b7c6-d192f062111e/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5723\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5723\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  th\u00e1nh<div>\u8056</div>"}, {"front": "phi\u1ebft (\u4e3f left-falling stroke, throw)", "id": "1448524349558", "back": "phi\u1ebft (\u4e3f left-falling stroke, throw)  <hr id=answer>  \u6487 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/ea165fa6-9b63-43ed-a1e0-2cd1e3e0c533/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6487\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6487\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "tr\u01b0\u1ee3ng (old unit of length)", "id": "1448524382502", "back": "tr\u01b0\u1ee3ng (old unit of length)  <hr id=answer>  \u4e08 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/2189d32c-3350-4cab-9d60-116486c4ad21/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u4e08\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u4e08\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u5e1b", "id": "1448524424960", "back": "\u5e1b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/73d46f7e-52ea-405c-a394-3583fc79e7b5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e1b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e1b\">Etymology</a> <hr id=answer>  b\u1ea1ch (silk)"}, {"front": "b\u1ea1ch (silk)", "id": "1448524424961", "back": "b\u1ea1ch (silk)  <hr id=answer>  \u5e1b <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/73d46f7e-52ea-405c-a394-3583fc79e7b5/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u5e1b\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u5e1b\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u0111\u1ec1 (propose, mention/nominate, upwards character stroke(calligraphy))", "id": "1448524474844", "back": "\u0111\u1ec1 (propose, mention/nominate, upwards character stroke(calligraphy))  <hr id=answer>  \u63d0 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/1c9f5005-6edb-45f1-8aa3-386fd90e4ede/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u63d0\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u63d0\">Etymology</a>"}, {"front": "\u0111\u00e3i (bad/wrong)", "id": "1448524506106", "back": "\u0111\u00e3i (bad/wrong)  <hr id=answer>  \u6b79 <br/> <a href=\"https://www.evernote.com/shard/s60/nl/1720770359/21030618-c2b4-4e01-b561-29bf6baffba2/\">Evernote</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.archchinese.com/mobile?find=\u6b79\">Animation</a> <br/> <a href=\"http://www.chineseetymology.org/CharacterEtymology.aspx?characterInput=\u6b79\">Etymology</a>"}]